linkedin.com/in/aunimoin github.com/aunimoin

SUMMARY

Highly organized, proactive team player with experience in Web Dev, Digital Ad-Tech and Market Research. Analytic problem-solver with extensive client management expertise who can prioritize tasks and deliver projects under tight deadlines. Specialist in leveraging global team structures and lover of efficient code and elegant web design.

SKILLS

JavaScript, HTML, CSS, React, Node, Express, Ruby, Rails, SQL, PostgreSQL, Git, MS Word-Excel-Powerpoint, MediaMath's TerminalOne, & Nielsen software (Spectra, Hispan-IQ, & Nitro).

PROFESSIONAL EXPERIENCE

Full-Stack Web Dev Immersive at General Assembly, New York, NY

Feb-May, 2018

- Food Trucks Only app React, Express.js, HTML, CSS, Yelp Fusion API & Google Maps API.
- > Design, develop and implement full-stack web apps. Diagnose bugs via Chrome Dev Tools.

Client Success Consultant at Proleadsoft, New York, NY

2016 - Present

> Prospecting new clients and consulting on pitch, copy, content, and design for Proleadsoft sales team.

Educational Video Content Editor/Builder at Learning Library TV, New York, NY

2016 - 2017

Edited tech experts' courses and worked with animators to produce MOOC style videos for IEEE and AAAS.

Business Development Manager at Quantformatix, Dhaka, Bangladesh

2015 - 2016

Sourced US financial services firms for offshore analytics company specializing in Big Data projects.

Platform Specialist at MediaMath, New York, NY

2013 - 2014

- Swiftly investigated and resolved Terminal One's (T1) campaign issues; created process documentation; performed data monitoring & troubleshooting with account, sales, product, API and UX/UI teams.
- > Prioritized and provided support for almost 2,000 T1 users. Worked with 8 global locations, closed over 1,700 tickets in 15 months, helped train 7 support employees, and maintained client communications.

Associate Client Manager at The Nielsen Company, New York, NY

2010 - 2012

- > Created detailed reports (120/yr) for Mars Chocolate and Wrigley Gum's marketing and sales teams by translating raw data to provide insights on consumer targeting, segmentation and consumption data analyses.
- Trained more than 50 analysts, managers, and directors on Nielsen's Spectra software.

Biz Dev & Market Analysis for Crowd Interactive, Boxhouse.org and BAMS.com, Brooklyn, NY

2008 - 2010

Process Engineer, Project Manager & Internal Consultant at Gerdau Ameristeel, Perth Amboy, NJ

2004 - 2007

Lead improvement projects by monitoring manufacturing processes, training employees and creating policies.

EDUCATION

Bachelor of Science in Electrical Engineering - Missouri University of Science and Technology

2004

Full-Stack Web Dev Immersive Program - General Assembly

Feb-May, 2018

OTHER INFORMATION

Languages & Interests: Fluent in Bengali. Bicycling, yoga, soccer, tennis, creating exotic chutneys/dips, sketching & painting and rescuing/fostering cats & dogs for BrooklynAnimalAction.org.